A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, General Correspondence FA735
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1958
  - Johnston…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Joint…, 1958 (Reel C-1276)
  - Jones…, 1958 (Reel C-1277)
  - Jordan…, 1958 (Reel C-1277)
  - Joseph…, 1958 (Reel C-1277)
  - Journal…, 1958 (Reel C-1277)
  - Jump Memorial Foundation, 1958 (Reel C-1277)
  - Junior…, 1958 (Reel C-1277)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, 1958 (Reel C-1277)
  - KA – KZ [General File]: KA – Klemperer, 1958 (Reel C-1277)
  - KA – KZ [General File]: Klemperer – KZ, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kahn…, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kansas, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kansas, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kaplan…, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Katsh, Abraham I., 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Katz…, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kaufamn…, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kaur…, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Keenan…, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Keep America Beautiful, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kelly…, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kennedy…, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kent…, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kentrschynskyj, Bohdan, 1958 (Reel C-1278)
  - Kentucky, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Kentucky Council on Public Higher Education, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Kentucky, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Kessler…, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - King…, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Kings…, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Klein…, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Kline…, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Knight…, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Knox College, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Koch…, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Korn, Alfred, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Korea, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Koslow, Jules, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Koussevitscky, Serge, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - Kuhn…, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - LA – LZ [General File]: LA – Lewit, 1958 (Reel C-1279)
  - LA – LZ [General File]: Lewit – LZ, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Landau…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lane…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lang…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lange…., 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Language Master, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Larson…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Latin American…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Latvala, Waino K., 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lawrence…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - League of Women Voters of the United States, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lebanon…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lee…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lefevre, R.A., 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Legendy, Rudolf, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Leonard…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Levine…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lewis…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Liberia…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Liberty…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Library of Congress, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lightfoot, William, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lincoln…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Linnik, Philip S., 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Little…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lindner…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Livingston…, 1958 (Reel C-1280)
  - Lockwood…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Loeks, C. David, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Loesch, William S., 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Loewenthal, Rudolf, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Logan…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - London…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Long…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Lopez, Joseph R., 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Los…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Los Angeles County Board of Supervisors, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Louisiana…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Louisville…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Lovelace…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Low…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Loyola University, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Lutheran…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Lynam Agricultural College, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Lynch…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Lyon…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - Lyons…, 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - McA – McZ [General File], 1958 (Reel C-1281)
  - McDonald…, 1958 (Reel C-1282)
  - McGill University, 1958 (Reel C-1282)
  - MA – MZ [General File]: MA – Michaud, 1958 (Reel C-1282)
  - MA – MZ [General File]: Michaud – MZ, 1958 (Reel C-1283)
  - Macalester College, 1958 (Reel C-1283)
  - Malaya…, 1958 (Reel C-1283)
  - Mann..., 1958 (Reel C-1283)
  - Marcus…, 1958 (Reel C-1283)
  - Marlboro School of Music, 1958 (Reel C-1283)
  - Marshall…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Martin…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Marygrove…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Maryland…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Mason…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Massachusetts…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - May…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Mayer…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Medical…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Merry…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Methodist…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Metropolitan…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Mexico City College, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Meyer…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Miami, University of (Coral Gables, Florida), 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Michaelhouse School, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Michigan…, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Michigan State University, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Michigan, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1284)
  - Michigan, University of – Attachments, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Middle Atlantic Association of Colleges and Business Administration, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Midwest…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Miller…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Ministry…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Minnesota, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Mitchell…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Moak, Lennox L., 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Modern Language Association (MLA), 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Montana…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Moore…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Morgan…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Morris…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Morse…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Mount…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Harvey Mudd College, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Mueller…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Murray…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Museum…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Museums Association…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - Myers…, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - NA – NZ [General File]: NA – Nagashima, 1958 (Reel C-1285)
  - NA – NZ [General File]: Nagashima – NZ, 1958 (Reel C-1286)
  - Natal, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1286)
  - National… (A-Z), 1958 (Reel C-1286)
  - National Association…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - National Conference…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - National Council…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - National Federation of Settlements and Neighborhood Centers, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - National Folk…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - National Guild of Community Music Schools, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - National Industrial Conference Board, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - National Information Bureau, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - National Military Industrial Conference, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - National Planning Association, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - National Science Foundation, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - Near East…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - Nebraska…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - Nellis, Mary T., 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - Nelson…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - Nepal…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - Netherlands…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - New…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - New Jersey…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - New York…, 1958 (Reel C-1287)
  - New York State…, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - New York University…, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - Newman…, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - Nigeria…, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - Nigerian…, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - North…, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - North Carolina, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - Northwestern University…, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - Norton…, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - Notre Dame, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - Nutrition Foundation, 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - OA – OZ [General File], 1958 (Reel C-1288)
  - Oberlin College, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Office of Education – Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (United States), 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Office of Intelligence Research and Analysis – Department o f State (United Sates), 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Ohio…, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Ohio State University, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Oklahoma…, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Oklahoma, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Old…, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Olson…, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Opera…, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Operations Mission to…, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Oregon…, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Organization of American States, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Ott…, 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Overseas Development (OD), 1958 (Reel C-1289)
  - Overseas Development (OD) Program Standard Report, 1958 (Reel C-1289, Reel C-1290)
  - Overseas Development (OD) Program Status Report, 1958 (Reel C-1290)
  - Our…, 1958 (Reel C-1290)
  - Owen…, 1958 (Reel C-1290)
  - Oxford…, 1958 (Reel C-1290)
  - PA – PZ [General File]: PA – Pisarek, 1958 (Reel C-1290)
  - PA – PZ [General File]: Pisarek – PZ, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Pacific…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Pakistan…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Pan American…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Pan American Institute of Geography and History, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Panamenco, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Park…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Parker…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Parsons…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Patterson…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Paul, D.P.S., 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Payne…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - (George) Peabody College for Teachers, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Peach, John R., 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Pearson…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Pennsylvania…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Pennsylvania, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Perkins…, 1958 (Reel C-1291)
  - Perry…, 1958 (Reel C-1292)
  - Peterson…, 1958 (Reel C-1292)
  - Petshek, Kirk R., 1958 (Reel C-1292)
  - Phelps-Stokes Fund, 1958 (Reel C-1292)
  - Philadelphia…, 1958 (Reel C-1292)
  - Philadelphia, City of, 1958 (Reel C-1292)
  - Philharmonic Symphony Society of New York, 1958 (Reel C-1292)
  - Philippines, University of the, 1958 (Reel C-1292)
  - Phillips…, 1958 (Reel C-1292)
  - Phoenix…, 1958 (Reel C-1292)
  - Physicians New Service, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Pierce…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Pierson, Frank C., 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Pittsburgh, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Polish…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Poole…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Population…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Porter…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Powell…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Presbyterian…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - President's…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Press Intelligence…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Price…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Prince…., 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Princeton University, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Product Design Company, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Public…, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Public Health Service, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - Purdue Richard B., 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - QA – QZ [General File], 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - RA – RZ [General File]: RA – Rozental, 1958 (Reel C-1293)
  - RA – RZ [General File]: Rozental – RZ, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Radio…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Ralston, George Lincoln, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rand Corporation, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rand Corporation - Attachments, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Randolph-Macon Women's College, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rangoon, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rao…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Real Estate, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Reed…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rehabilitation…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Research…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Resources for the Future, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Revell Company (Fleming H.), 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Reynolds…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Reynolds, Lloyd G., 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rhode Island…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rhodes…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Ryme University, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rias, Inc., 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rice…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Richardson…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Ritchie…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Roberts…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Robertson…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rochester…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rockefeller…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rockford…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rodgers…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Rogers…, 1958 (Reel C-1294)
  - Roosevelt University, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Rosary…, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Rose…, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Rosen…, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Rosenberg…, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Rosenthal…, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Ross…, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Ross, Arthur M., 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Royal…, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Royal Geographical Society of Australia, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Russell…, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Rutgers University, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Ryan…, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - Ryukyu…, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - SA – SZ [General File]: SA – Seale, 1958 (Reel C-1295)
  - SA – SZ [General File]: Seale – Spruhl, 1958 (Reel C-1296)
  - SA – SZ [General File]: Spruhl – SZ, 1958 (Reel C-1297)
  - Saarland, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1297)
  - Saint…, 1958 (Reel C-1297)
  - St. Coletta School, 1958 (Reel C-1297)
  - St. Joseph…, 1958 (Reel C-1297)
  - St. Joseph's…., 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - St. Mary's…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - St. Tsirimonis, Constantin, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Salem…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Salvation Army, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - San…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - San Francisco State College, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Sanders…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Sanderson…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Santa…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Saturday Review (of Literature), 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Save the Children Federation, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Scheyer, Joseph H., 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Schmidt…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Schneider…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - School…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Schultz…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Science…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Scott…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Scranton, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Seattle…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Senate…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Senior…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Seroff, Richard, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Shaw…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Silberman…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Silver…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Simmons…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Simon…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Simpson…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Singer…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Singh…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Sister…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Sisters…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Skinner…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Slater…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Small…, 1958 (Reel C-1298)
  - Smith…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Snyder…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Snyder, Robert, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Social…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Society…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - South…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - South African…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Southern…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Southern California, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Spencer…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Springfield College, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Spurrier, Dawson, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Staley…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Standard…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Stanford Research Institute, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Stanford University, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Stanley…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Stark…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - State Department (United States), 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Stein…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Stephens…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Stevens…, 1958 (Reel C-1299)
  - Stewart…, 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Stockton, John B., 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Stone…, 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Stout…, 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Stuart…, 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Sudan…, 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Swarthmore…., 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Syracuse University, 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Syria, 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - TA – TZ [General File], 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Taylor…, 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Taylor, Paul S., 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Technical…, 1958 (Reel C-1300)
  - Technical Assistance Information Clearing House, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Tehran, University of (Iran), 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Temple…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Tennessee, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Tennessee, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Texas…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Texas Agricultural and Mechanical College, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Texas, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Theatre…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Thomas…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Thompson…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Thompson, Frank, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Tokyo…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Tolstoy Foundation, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Toronto, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Tri-…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Trinity…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Tucker…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Tufts University, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Tulane University, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Turner…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Turkey…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Twentieth Century Fund, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Typewriter Students Institute, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Tulsa…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - UA – UZ [General File], 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - UNESCO, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - Union…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - United…, 1958 (Reel C-1301)
  - United Kingdom, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - United Nations, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - United States…, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - United States Information Agency, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - United States Information Service, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - United States National Commission for UNESCO, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - University College…, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - University College of Rhodesia and Nyasaland, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - UNLA (Community Improvement through Adult Education), 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - Upper…, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - Utah, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - VA – VZ, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - Van…, 1958 (Reel C-1302)
  - Vienna, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1303)
  - Virginia, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1303)
  - Von…, 1958 (Reel C-1303)
  - WA – WZ [General File]: WA – Wilder, 1958 (Reel C-1303)
  - WA – WZ [General File]: Wilder – WZ, 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Walker…, 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Ward…, 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Ward, F. Champion, 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Warialshah, Sayyed Muhammed, 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Warren…, 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Washington, State College of, 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Washington University (St. Louis), 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Washington, University of (Seattle), 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Wayne State University, 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - West…, 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Western…, 1958 (Reel C-1304)
  - Western College for Women, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Wheeler…, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Wheeler, Phillip R., 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - White…, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Wilsey and Ham, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Wilson…, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Williams…, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Wisconsin, University of, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - WKNO-TV (Memphis Community Television Foundation), 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Wolf…, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Wolfe…, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Women for the United Nations, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Wood…, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Woods…, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - World…, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - World Book Encyclopedia, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - World Brotherhood, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - WQED (Channel 13, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania), 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Wright…, 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - XA – XZ [General File], 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - YA – YZ [General File], 1958 (Reel C-1305)
  - Yale University, 1958 (Reel C-1306)
  - Young…, 1958 (Reel C-1306)
  - Young Men's and Women's Christian Association (YMCA / YWCA), 1958 (Reel C-1306)
  - ZA – ZZ {General File], 1958 (Reel C-1306)
  - Bibliography of Related Materials, General Correspondence, 1958 (Reel C-1306)
    List of books, pamphlets, articles, reports, etc. related to the General Correspondence files for 1958.
- General Correspondence, 1959
  A bibliography of related books, pamphlets, articles, reports, etc. related to the General Correspondence files for 1959 is filed at the end of this series.
  - AA – AZ [General File]: AA – Alverno College, 1959 (Reel C-1306)
  - AA – AZ [General File]: Alverno – AZ, 1959 (Reel C-1307)
  - Action Housing Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1307)
  - Advisory Committee on International Training and Research (ITR), 1959 (Reel C-1307)
  - Africa, 1959 (Reel C-1307)
  - African Fair, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - Agriculture, U.S. Department of, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - Akhtar, Aftab, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - Alabama, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - Alabama, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - Alaska, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - Alexander, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - All…, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - Allen…, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - Allen, Raymond B., 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - Allison Mailing Lists Corporation, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - American…, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Sciences, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - American Alumni Council, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - American Association…, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - American Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - American Bar Association, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - American Committee…, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - American Council on Education, 1959 (Reel C-1308)
  - American Foundation…, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Friends…, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Institute…, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Library Association, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American National Exhibition in Moscow, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Political Science Association, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Psychological Association, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Public Welfare Association, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Records Management Association, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Red Cross, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Society, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Society for Public Administration, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Society of African Culture, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - American Symphony Orchestra League, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Amherst College, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Anderson…, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Andes, University of the, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Anti-Defamation League, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Antioch College, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Area I (Peace), 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Area II (Democracy), 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Area III (Economic Development), 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Area IV (Education), 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Area V (Behavioral Sciences), 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Argentina, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Arizona State University, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Armour Research Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Arnold, Edwin G., 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Asia…, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Asia Foundation, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Associated…, 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Associated Negro Press, Inc., 1959 (Reel C-1309)
  - Association…, 1959 (Reel C-1310)
  - Association for Asian Studies, 1959 (Reel C-1310)
  - Association of Higher Education, 1959 (Reel C-1310)
  - Assumption College, 1959 (Reel C-1310)
  - Austria, 1959 (Reel C-1310)
  - BA – BZ [General File]: BA – Bertocci, 1959 (Reel C-1310)
  - BA – BZ [General File]: Bertocci – Brooklyn Museum, 1959 (Reel C-1311)
  - BA – BZ [General File]: Brooklyn Museum – BZ, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Bailey…, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Baker…, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Baker, Jack, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Baughman, George W., 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Belgian Congo, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Bell…, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Bender, Kent, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Bennett…, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Bird, Remsen, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Black…, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Blackburn College, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Board…, 1959 (Reel C-1312)
  - Bolivia…, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Boston University, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Boys…, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Boys Clubs of America, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Boys Clubs of New York, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Brauer, Ralph W., 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Brazil, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Brazil, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Bridgeport, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - British Academy, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - British Council, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Brookings Institution, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Brown…, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Bucknell University, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Buenos Aires, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Buffalo, University of, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Bureau…, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Burelle's Press Clipping Bureau, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Burke…, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Burkhardt, Frederick, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Burma…, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Business Council for International Understanding, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Butler…, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - Butts, R. Freeman, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - CA – CZ [General File]: CA – Cammack, 1959 (Reel C-1313)
  - CA – CZ [General File]: Cammack – Citron, 1959 (Reel C-1314)
  - CA – CZ [General File]: Citron – Cronin, 1959 (Reel C-1315)